♪A light shines on me♪
نور يضيء علي ♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
ورقة تسقط على الأرض
♪A person♪
شخص ♪
♪Living in another world♪
العيش في عالم آخر ♪
♪A beating heart♪
قلب ينبض ♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪ رياح لطيفة ♪
♪You bring me the light♪
أحضر لي النور
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
♪ الوقوع في الحب في لحظة ♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪ قصة تتكشف صفحة بصفحة
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
♪ قلب وحيد يسخن ببطء ♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪ نجمة متلألئة ♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪ متجه لمقابلتك ♪
♪You mean everything to me in reality or in my dreams♪
♪ أنت تعني لي كل شيء في الواقع أو في أحلامي ♪
=The Next Stop W= (Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
= المحطة التالية W = (مقتبس من المسلسل التلفزيوني W - عالمان)
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
(To be continued)
(يتبع)
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Dad! Liu Feng!
أبي! ليو فنغ!
Dad, didn't you say
أبي ، لم تقل
that you wanted a happy ending?
أنك تريد نهاية سعيدة؟
Why did you kill another person
لماذا قتلت شخصا آخر
and pin the murder on Jiang Zhe?
وتعلق القتل على جيانغ زهي؟
Dad.
أب.
Ah!
آه!
Hello, Yanzhu.
مرحبا يانتشو.
(Hello, Liu Feng.)
(مرحبًا ، ليو فنغ.)
(What happened to my dad?)
(ماذا حدث لأبي؟)
You saw it too, right?
لقد رأيت ذلك أيضًا ، أليس كذلك؟
His face is gone.
ذهب وجهه.
Shoot Lu Shenshen dead with a gun
أطلق النار على لو شينشن ميتًا بمسدس
and paint a gun in Jiang Zhe's hand.
ورسم مسدسًا في يد جيانغ زهي.
Then let the police chase him.
ثم دع الشرطة تطارده.
I heard a voice
سمعت صوتا
giving orders to Mr. Wu.
إعطاء الأوامر للسيد وو.
(It seemed like he was manipulated,)
(يبدو أنه تم التلاعب به ،)
(drawing as requested.)
(الرسم حسب الطلب.)
That means
هذا يعني
my dad's face became like that
أصبح وجه أبي هكذا
because of the murderer.
بسبب القاتل.
Where is the murderer now?
اين القاتل الان؟
How does he manipulate my dad?
كيف يتلاعب بوالدي؟
How can I help my dad?
كيف يمكنني مساعدة والدي؟
(Yanzhu, don't be worried.)
(يانتشو ، لا تقلق.)
(I haven't figured it out.)
(لم أحسب ذلك.)
But now it's clear
لكن الأمر واضح الآن
that those things that happened in the comic world
أن تلك الأشياء التي حدثت في عالم القصص المصورة
were drawn by my dad
رسمها والدي
on the orders of the murderer.
بأمر القاتل.
What happened to Jiang Zhe?
ماذا حدث لجيانغ زهي؟
The murderer killed Lu Shenshen
قتل القاتل لو شينشن
and pinned it on Jiang Zhe.
وتثبيته على جيانغ زهي.
What?
ماذا؟
Lu Shenshen is dead?
لو Shenshen مات؟
That bad man!
هذا الرجل السيئ!
How could he kill her?
كيف يمكنه قتلها؟
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
You'd better leave there.
من الأفضل أن تغادر هناك.
It's quite dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير للغاية.
No, I can't.
لا ، لا أستطيع.
Now only Jiang Zhe can save my dad,
الآن فقط جيانغ زهي يمكنه إنقاذ والدي ،
so I have to save him.
لذلك علي أن أنقذه.
Take care of yourself first.
اعتني بنفسك أولا.
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
Is it you?
هل هذا انت؟
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Answer me.
يجيبني.
(Pull yourself together.)
(اضبط نفسك.)
(I can't be there now,)
(لا أستطيع أن أكون هناك الآن ،)
(so you have to treat yourself.)
(لذلك عليك أن تعامل نفسك).
(First, remember to inject antibiotics.)
(تذكر أولاً أن تحقن المضادات الحيوية.)
(Then take the bullet out.)
(ثم ​​أخرج الرصاصة).
(It hurts, but hang in there,)
(هذا مؤلم ، لكن انتظر هناك ،)
(or the wound will fester.)
(أو سوف يتفاقم الجرح.)
(After removing the bullet,)
(بعد إزالة الرصاصة)
(disinfect the wound with alcohol)
(تطهير الجرح بالكحول)
(and suture it with suture thread and needle.)
(وخياطته بخيط خياطة وإبرة.)
(I will be there as soon as possible.)
(سأكون هناك في أقرب وقت ممكن.)
(Take good care of yourself.)
(اهتم بنفسك جيدا.)
Wu Yanzhu.
وو يان تشو.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
The murderer
القاتل
just tried to drag me
فقط حاولت جرني
to the comic world through the drawing tablet.
إلى عالم القصص المصورة من خلال لوح الرسم.
I turned off the power,
أوقفت الكهرباء ،
and he disappeared.
واختفى.
That means you can cut off contact
هذا يعني أنه يمكنك قطع الاتصال
with the murderer by that.
مع القاتل بذلك.
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
What do we do with Mr. Wu?
ماذا نفعل مع السيد وو؟
I want to try again with a dream.
أريد أن أحاول مرة أخرى بحلم.
Right.
يمين.
You can go back to a very early time
يمكنك العودة إلى وقت مبكر جدًا
and change the dream
وتغيير الحلم
which Jiang Zhe had before his family died
الذي مات جيانغ زهي قبل وفاة عائلته
to permanently cut it off.
لقطعها بشكل دائم.
Right?
يمين؟
Right.
يمين.
But now I dare not turn on the tablet.
لكن الآن لا أجرؤ على تشغيل الجهاز اللوحي.
I'm afraid that the murderer
أخشى أن يكون القاتل
is just waiting for me.
فقط ينتظرني.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
I can't draw anything now.
لا يمكنني رسم أي شيء الآن.
Hmm.
همم.
Wu Yanzhu.
وو يان تشو.
It's been a month.
لقد مر شهر.
It's been a month?
لقد مر شهر؟
I finally see you.
أراك أخيرًا.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Let's go somewhere.
لنذهب الى مكان ما.
I haven't talked to anyone for a long time.
لم أتحدث إلى أي شخص منذ فترة طويلة.
I'm quite happy.
انا سعيد جدا.
I thought
اعتقدت
you were...
كنت...
Why?
لماذا؟
You gave me medicine
أعطيتني دواء
and told me the treatment.
وأخبرني بالعلاج.
How could I die?
كيف اموت؟
But judging by the look on your face,
لكن بالحكم من نظرة وجهك ،
you haven't found a solution yet.
لم تجد حلا بعد.
I was looking forward to it.
كنت أتطلع إليها.
After all,
بعد كل ذلك،
when everyone suspected that I was the murderer,
عندما اشتبه الجميع في أنني القاتل ،
only you saved me without hesitation.
أنت الوحيد الذي أنقذني دون تردد.
Sorry.
آسف.
You don't need to apologize.
لا داعي للاعتذار.
You have saved me many times.
لقد أنقذتني عدة مرات.
Hungry?
جوعان؟
Let's go get something to eat.
دعنا نذهب للحصول على شيء لنأكله.
There's nothing at home.
لا يوجد شيء في المنزل.
Here.
هنا.
But you're wanted now
لكنك مطلوب الآن
and have been hunted down for a month.
وقد تم اصطيادهم لمدة شهر.
Instead of thinking about how to clear your name,
بدلاً من التفكير في كيفية مسح اسمك ،
you're eating ice cream with me.
أنت تأكل الآيس كريم معي.
What are you thinking?
بماذا تفكر؟
Maybe I'm set
ربما أنا مستعد
to have a sad ending.
أن يكون لها نهاية حزينة.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
How about going shopping together
ماذا عن الذهاب للتسوق معا
after we eat up ice cream?
بعد أن نأكل الآيس كريم؟
In such a situation,
في مثل هذا الموقف،
you're still thinking about shopping?
ما زلت تفكر في التسوق؟
As long as I'm with you,
طالما أنا معك ،
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Probably I can't buy you expensive clothes.
ربما لا أستطيع شراء ملابس باهظة الثمن لك.
Save a little money for us.
ادخر القليل من المال لنا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
♪Looking out at you from a lighthouse far away♪
ينظر إليك من منارة بعيدة ♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
الحجامة بأشعة الشمس المشرقة
♪Can it♪
♪ هل يمكن ♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪ تدفئ قلبك؟
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪